worldwide-invest.org 2015-05-21

# Privacy Policy

##  [Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements]() [](http://worldwide-invest.org/privacy_policy.php#top)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

##  [Registration]() [](http://worldwide-invest.org/privacy_policy.php#top)

Registration is not necessary for the public to use this Web site. However, members must register in order to gain access to adding threads to the Web site. During registration, you must complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give us contact information. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.We are the sole owner of the information collected on this Web site.

##  [Inappropriate Language]() [](http://worldwide-invest.org/privacy_policy.php#top)

The use of inappropriate or offensive language is not permitted in these forums. Inappropriate or offensive language includes, but is not limited to, any language or content that is sexually oriented, sexually suggestive or abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, profane, hateful, or that contains racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable material of any kind. We ask that you please be considerate to other members in the forums when posting your messages.

##  [Posting Links]() [](http://worldwide-invest.org/privacy_policy.php#top)

Our policy on linking to other forums is pretty simple. Members may link to any other site that provides information that helps answer another member's question or is just of general interest to members of that particular forum. One of the most basic tenets of the Web is the open exchange of information.

##  [Security]() [](http://worldwide-invest.org/privacy_policy.php#top)

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

##  [Ad Servers]() [](http://worldwide-invest.org/privacy_policy.php#top)

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:  
 **If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email:[Here](http://worldwide-invest.org/sendmessage.php)**

##  [Opt-Out Policy]() [](http://worldwide-invest.org/privacy_policy.php#top)

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:  
Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.  
Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our user

##  [Consent]() [](http://worldwide-invest.org/privacy_policy.php#top)

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us.

##  [Disclaimer]() [](http://worldwide-invest.org/privacy_policy.php#top)

reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

##  [Changes in this Privacy Statement]() [](http://worldwide-invest.org/privacy_policy.php#top)

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.  

**PLEASE NOTE that opting out of the ad-serving cookie does not mean that you will stop seeing either pop up advertising or banner ads embedded in websites! You can control many pop ups by using free software available on the Internet or by disabling JavaScript on your browser. DoubleClick has no control over the use or frequency of pop-up ads employed by website publishers or software manufacturers.** For more information about pop-up ads, please [click here](http://worldwide-invest.org/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/faq.asp#pop-ups) **.** | **DoubleClick Opt-out Click link below**  
---|---
